{
    "id": "8bffe41da49e43fe97aff807135166ef",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Get",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a638dcc7bbfd41a28de40ec1edc4ac99",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Get",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I don't mind getting ................................ early if there is a good reason to.",
                    "description": "To get up is to rise from bed after sleeping.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "off",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is no room on the bus. Let's get ..................................... again.",
                    "description": "To get off a vehicle is to leave a vehicle.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "in",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Get ..................................... and I will drive you to the station.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It took me a long time to get ......................................... the disappointment.",
                    "description": "To get over is to overcome a difficulty.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "off",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The robbers got ...................................... with diamonds worth millions of dollars.",
                    "description": "To get away is to escape.",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "away",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The supervisor asked the employees to get ............................................... the job quickly.",
                    "description": "To get on with work is to perform work.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "with",
                        "on with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I tried calling but I couldn't get ............................................ to him.",
                    "description": "To get through to somebody is to be able to talk to them via telephone.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "through",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I find it very difficult to get .......................................... on my meager salary.",
                    "description": "To get by is to manage to live with great difficulty.",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The setbacks got him ........................................",
                    "description": "If something gets you down, it makes you very unhappy.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can we get ........................................ for lunch on the weekend?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "together",
                        "around"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His stupidity got him ........................................... trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "through",
                        "onto",
                        "into"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rumors get ....................................... fast.",
                    "description": "When rumors get around, they spread.",
                    "answers": [
                        "around",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}